Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 5. Fund Raising and Related Materials, 1965-1974; 5; About 2 linear feet Boxes: 41 - 46 Folders: 552 - 680
  - American Heritage Award Mailing (Code AMH) (Folder 589, Box 44)
  - American Museum of Natural History (Folder 590, Box 44)
  - American Schizophrenia Association (Folder 591, Box 44)
  - American Shakespeare Festival; IAGO (Folder 592, Box 44)
  - American Veterans Committee (Folder 593, Box 44)
  - Americans for Democratic Action (Folder 594, Box 44)
  - Avant (Folder 595, Box 44)
  - Bonniers - Rental/PP (Folder 596, Box 44)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists (Folder 597, Box 44)
  - Center Magazine (Folder 598, Box 44)
  - Charles Scribner’s Book-buyers (Folder 599, Box 44)
  - Citizens Union, Inquiry re: Fall 1970 (Folder 600, Box 44)
  - Committee to Rescue Italian Art - Contri. (Rental/PP) (Folder 601, Box 44)
  - Common Cause (Names in the News) (Folder 602, Box 44)
  - Conservation Foundation (Folder 603, Box 44)
  - The Coolidge Co. - Carol Peles (Folder 604, Box 44)
  - BW-10 (Rental-Coolidge Co.) (Folder 605, Box 44)
  - CORE (Folder 606, Box 44)
  - Council on Economic Priorities (Folder 607, Box 44)
  - Dart Industries (Computer Names) 230 Park Ave. NY 10017 (Folder 608, Box 44)
  - Defenders of Wildlife (Folder 609, Box 44)
  - Dependable Mailing Lists (Rachel Carson Trust List) (Folder 610, Box 44)
  - Devin Adair NATURE (Rental/PP) (Folder 611, Box 44)
  - Donors to Appeal for Needy Actors& Artists (Coolidge AP 4) LOGE (Folder 612, Box 44)
  - E. J. Krane List Broker; Int. Rescue Comm. American Civil Liberties Union etc. (Folder 613, Box 44)
  - Encounter (Folder 614, Box 44)
  - Englewood Mailing List # 111, Large Donor List (Folder 615, Box 44)
  - Environmental Action (Folder 616, Box 44)
  - Environmental Action Bulletin Subscribers (Rodale Press, Emmaus, Pa 18049 (Folder 617, Box 44)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, Fall 1970 (Folder 618, Box 44)
  - Friends of the Earth (Folder 619, Box 44)
  - Gilbert Jonas (NAACP) (Holy Land Env.) (Merged Lib. List) (Folder 620, Box 44)
  - Holy Land Conservation Fund, Inc. (Folder 621, Box 44)
  - Hudson Guild, Attn. Connie Kelley (Folder 622, Box 44)
  - International Rescue Committee (See E.J. Krane ) (Folder 623, Box 44)
  - Izaak Walton League of America (Folder 624, Box 44)
  - Keep America Beautiful, Inc. (Folder 625, Box 44)
  - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council (Folder 626, Box 44)
  - The Mail Chute Corresp. Re: Lists (Folder 627, Box 44)
  - Mark Cross - Rental/PP (Folder 628, Box 44)
  - Musician’s Aid Code “VIO” (Folder 629, Box 44)
  - Musician’s Aid Soc. Coolidge; V-10 (Folder 630, Box 44)
  - National Audubon Society - Exchange Mailing - Spring 1970, code R.B. (Folder 631, Box 44)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (Folder 632, Box 45)
  - The National Conference on State Parks (Folder 633, Box 45)
  - National Parks Assoc. 1967-73 (Folder 634, Box 45)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, Nov. ‘70-’71 (Folder 635, Box 45)
  - National Wildlife Federation (Folder 636, Box 45)
  - New York Botanical Gardens (Folder 637, Box 45)
  - New York Social Register (Folder 638, Box 45)
  - N.Y. Zoological Society (Folder 639, Box 45)
  - People in Places - G. Reade (Folder 640, Box 45)
  - Planned Parenthood (Folder 641, Box 45)
  - Professional Sources and Lists Fund Raising (Folder 642, Box 45)
  - The Progressive - Act. (Rental PP) (Folder 643, Box 45)
  - Protestant Federation (Folder 644, Box 45)
  - Raymond - Loew Associates - - List 9 (Folder 645, Box 45)
  - Realities Mag. (Coolidge) OUI (Folder 646, Box 45)
  - Reports on Mailings, Reports: Rosenthal analyses (Folder 647, Box 45)
  - SANE (Folder 648, Box 45)
  - Save - a - Life League, VIS (Folder 649, Box 45)
  - Save the Redwoods League, SAU (Folder 650, Box 45)
  - Schneinder& Rich Assoc. - (Native Am. Rights Fund) (Voter Education Project) (Folder 651, Box 45)
  - Scholarship Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality; Attn. Mr. Peterson (Folder 652, Box 45)
  - SEDFRE (Folder 653, Box 45)
  - SIECUS (Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S.), KEY (Folder 654, Box 45)
  - Sierra Club (Folder 655, Box 45)
  - Spanish Refuge Aid, Fall 1970 (Folder 656, Box 45)
  - Summer Social Reg. People in Places rental; AES (Folder 657, Box 45)
  - Walter Karl, Inc. (Armonk, N.Y. 10504) (Folder 658, Box 45)
  - Wild Flowers of America (Crown Publishers) (Folder 659, Box 45)
  - Wilderness Society, March 1970; Louise Talbert (Folder 660, Box 45)
  - Winston Churchill Memorial Lib., BST (Folder 661, Box 45)
  - Winston Churchill Memorial Lib., SPS (Folder 662, Box 45)
  - Winston Churchill Memorial Lib., SP (Folder 663, Box 45)
  - World Wildlife Fund, Fall 1970 (Folder 664, Box 45)
  - SHPC - Background Information - Seymour Memo, etc. (Folder 665, Box 46)
  - Christmas Party Dec. 8, 1971; Wed. (Folder 666, Box 46)
  - Chronology of S.H. (Folder 667, Box 46)
  - SHPC - Committees (Folder 668, Box 46)
  - Contacts (Folder 669, Box 46)
  - SHPC - Expenses - N.M. (Folder 670, Box 46)
  - Fact Sheet (Folder 671, Box 46)
  - SHPC - Intervenors (Folder 672, Box 46)
  - SHPC - Hikes (Folder 673, Box 46)
  - Memos - Staff& Committees (Folder 674, Box 46)
  - Newsletters and Similar Publications (Folder 675, Box 46)
  - SHPC - Newsletter Materials (Folder 676, Box 46)
  - SHPC Newsletter Materials (Folder 677, Box 46)
  - Shareholders 1974 (Folder 678, Box 46)
  - Application for S.H. Speakers (Folder 679, Box 46)
  - Board (Stationary) (Folder 680, Box 46)
- 6. Hearings, 1965-1974; 6; About 4 linear feet Boxes: 74 - 62 Folders: 681 - 735
  Series contains materials concerning hearings before the Federal Power Commission, Congressional sub-committees, and New York State environmental groups. This series includes the official stenographic transcripts of the FPC hearings, 1964-1970, arranged chronologically. (For additional Stenographic Transcripts please see the H.R.V.C. Collection, Series 3, Boxes 3-7)
  - Hearings 1965-66 (Folder 681, Box 47)
  - Statement of: (Folder 682, Box 47)
  - House of Representatives Report of Proceedings; Committee on Merchant Marines Storm King Mountain Projects Hearings (Folder 683, Box 47)
  - Congressional Hearings, 1974 (Folder 684, Box 47)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report (Folder 685, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Pre-Hearing Conference Vol. 29 (Folder 686, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Pre-Hearing Conference Vol. 30-31 (Folder 687, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Volume No. 32-A, Part 2 of 3 (Folder 688, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Volume No. 32-B, Part 3 of 3; and 33, Part 1 of 2 (Folder 689, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 34 and 34 A (Folder 690, Box 49)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 35 - 36 (Folder 691, Box 49)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 37 (Folder 692, Box 49)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 39 - 40 (Folder 693, Box 50)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 41 - 42 (Folder 694, Box 50)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 43 - 44 (Folder 695, Box 50)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 45 - 46 (Folder 696, Box 51)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 47 - 48 (Folder 697, Box 51)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 49 - 50 (Folder 698, Box 51)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 51 - 52 (Folder 699, Box 52)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 53 - 54 (Folder 700, Box 52)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 55 - 56 (Folder 701, Box 52)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 57 - 58 (Folder 702, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 63 - 64 (Folder 703, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 65 - 66 (Folder 704, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 67 - 68 (Folder 705, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 69 - 70 (Folder 706, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 71 - 72 (Folder 707, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 73 - 74 (Folder 708, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 75 - 76 (Folder 709, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 77 - 78 (Folder 710, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 79 (Folder 711, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 80 - 81 (Folder 712, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 82 - 83 (Folder 713, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 84 - 85 (Folder 714, Box 56)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 86 - 87 (Folder 715, Box 56)
  - Official stenographers’ Report, Vol. 88 - 89 (Folder 716, Box 56)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 90 - 91 (Folder 717, Box 57)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 92 - 93 (Folder 718, Box 57)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 94 - 95 (Folder 719, Box 57)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 96 - 97 (Folder 720, Box 58)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 98 - 99 (Folder 721, Box 58)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 100 - 101 (Folder 722, Box 58)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 102 - 103 (Folder 723, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 104 - 105 (Folder 724, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 106 - 107 (Folder 725, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 109 - 110 (Folder 726, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 111 - 112 (Folder 727, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 113 - 114 - 115 (Folder 728, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 116 - 117 (Folder 729, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 118 - 119 (Folder 730, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 120 - 121 (Folder 731, Box 61)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 122 - 123 (Folder 732, Box 61)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 124 - 125 (Folder 733, Box 62)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 126 - 128 (Folder 734, Box 62)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 129 - 130 (Folder 735, Box 62)
- 7. Ledoux, Louis Pierre, 1964-1968; 7; About 1.5 linear feet Boxes: 63 - 66 Folders: 736 - 797
  Series correspondence relating to the Storm King case, collected by Mr. Ledoux, a member of the Board of Directors of Scenic Hudson. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically.
  - Hearings 1965-66 (Folder 681, Box 47)
  - Statement of: (Folder 682, Box 47)
  - House of Representatives Report of Proceedings; Committee on Merchant Marines& Fisheries; Storm King Mountain Projects Hearings (Folder 683, Box 47)
  - Congressional Hearings, 1974 (Folder 684, Box 47)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report (Folder 685, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Pre-Hearing Conference Vol. 29 (Folder 686, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Pre-Hearing Conference Vol. 30-31 (Folder 687, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Volume No. 32-A, Part 2 of 3 (Folder 688, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Volume No. 32-B, Part 3 of 3; and 33, Part 1 of 2 (Folder 689, Box 48)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 34 and 34 A (Folder 690, Box 49)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 35 - 36 (Folder 691, Box 49)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 37 (Folder 692, Box 49)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 39 - 40 (Folder 693, Box 50)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 41 - 42 (Folder 694, Box 50)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 43 - 44 (Folder 695, Box 50)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 45 - 46 (Folder 696, Box 51)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 47 - 48 (Folder 697, Box 51)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 49 - 50 (Folder 698, Box 51)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 51 - 52 (Folder 699, Box 52)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 53 - 54 (Folder 700, Box 52)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 55 - 56 (Folder 701, Box 52)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 57 - 58 (Folder 702, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 63 - 64 (Folder 703, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 65 - 66 (Folder 704, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 67 - 68 (Folder 705, Box 53)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 69 - 70 (Folder 706, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 71 - 72 (Folder 707, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 73 - 74 (Folder 708, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 75 - 76 (Folder 709, Box 54)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 77 - 78 (Folder 710, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 79 (Folder 711, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 80 - 81 (Folder 712, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 82 - 83 (Folder 713, Box 55)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 84 - 85 (Folder 714, Box 56)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 86 - 87 (Folder 715, Box 56)
  - Official stenographers’ Report, Vol. 88 - 89 (Folder 716, Box 56)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 90 - 91 (Folder 717, Box 57)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 92 - 93 (Folder 718, Box 57)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 94 - 95 (Folder 719, Box 57)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 96 - 97 (Folder 720, Box 58)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 98 - 99 (Folder 721, Box 58)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 100 - 101 (Folder 722, Box 58)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 102 - 103 (Folder 723, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 104 - 105 (Folder 724, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 106 - 107 (Folder 725, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 109 - 110 (Folder 726, Box 59)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 111 - 112 (Folder 727, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 113 - 114 - 115 (Folder 728, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 116 - 117 (Folder 729, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 118 - 119 (Folder 730, Box 60)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 120 - 121 (Folder 731, Box 61)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 122 - 123 (Folder 732, Box 61)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 124 - 125 (Folder 733, Box 62)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 126 - 128 (Folder 734, Box 62)
  - Official Stenographers’ Report, Vol. 129 - 130 (Folder 735, Box 62)
  - A (Folder 736, Box 63)
  - Appalachian Highlands Association (Folder 737, Box 63)
  - B (Folder 738, Box 63)
  - Bucknall (Folder 739, Box 63)
  - Butzel, A.K. (Folder 740, Box 63)
  - C (Folder 741, Box 63)
  - Callahan, Thomas, P. (Folder 742, Box 63)
  - Clippings (Folder 743, Box 63)
  - Consolidated Edison Co. (Folder 744, Box 63)
  - Cope, James (Folder 745, Box 63)
  - Cornwall; Local (Folder 746, Box 63)
  - Cornwall - on - Hudson (Folder 747, Box 63)
  - D (Folder 748, Box 63)
  - Duggan, Mr. and Mrs. Stephen P., Jr. (Folder 749, Box 63)
  - E (Folder 750, Box 63)
  - F (Folder 751, Box 63)
  - Field, William Osgood (Folder 752, Box 63)
  - G (Folder 753, Box 64)
  - Goddess, Lynn B.; SHPC (Folder 754, Box 64)
  - H (Folder 755, Box 64)
  - Harold L. Oram, Inc. (Public Relations) (Folder 756, Box 64)
  - Harvard University (Folder 757, Box 64)
  - Hudson River Conservation Society (Folder 758, Box 64)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission (Folder 759, Box 64)
  - I (Folder 760, Box 64)
  - J (Folder 761, Box 64)
  - K (Folder 762, Box 64)
  - Kitzmiller, Wm. Michael (Folder 763, Box 64)
  - L (Folder 764, Box 64)
  - Lamb, Dr. and Mrs. Albert R., Jr. (Folder 765, Box 64)
  - Ledoux Notes re: Scenic Hudson Pres. Conf. (Folder 766, Box 64)
  - M (Folder 767, Box 64)
  - Mathews, Nancy - SHPC (Folder 768, Box 64)
  - Mieczkowski, Lee (Mrs. Edward) (Folder 769, Box 64)
  - N (Folder 770, Box 65)
  - The Nature Conservatory (Folder 771, Box 65)
  - New York City (Folder 772, Box 65)
  - New York State (Folder 773, Box 65)
  - Ottinger, Richard L. (Folder 774, Box 65)
  - O (Folder 775, Box 65)
  - P (Folder 776, Box 65)
  - R (Folder 777, Box 65)
  - Rockefeller, Gov. Nelson A. (Folder 778, Box 65)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas (Folder 779, Box 65)
  - Rothschild, Leo O. (Folder 780, Box 65)
  - S (Folder 781, Box 65)
  - Scenic Hudson; 1964-65 (Folder 782, Box 65)
  - Scenic Hudson; 1966 (Folder 783, Box 65)
  - Scenic Hudson Jan. - Aug. 1967 (Folder 784, Box 65)
  - Scenic Hudson; Sept. - Dec. 1967 (Folder 785, Box 66)
  - Scenic Hudson; 1968 (Folder 786, Box 66)
  - Scenic Hudson; Misc. and Undated (Folder 787, Box 66)
  - Sive, David (Folder 788, Box 66)
  - T (Folder 789, Box 66)
  - Unidentified (Folder 790, Box 66)
  - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (Folder 791, Box 66)
  - U.S. Department of Interior (Folder 792, Box 66)
  - V (Folder 793, Box 66)
  - Vandivert, Rod; 1965 - Sept. 1966 (Folder 794, Box 66)
  - Vandivert, Rod; Oct. - Dec. 1966 (Folder 795, Box 66)
  - Vandivert, Rod; 1967 - 68 (Folder 796, Box 66)
  - W (Folder 797, Box 66)
- 8. Legal Papers, 1964-1974; 8; About 3.5 linear feet Boxes: 67 - 77 Folders: 798 - 996
  Series contains briefs, petitions, motions, and other legal documents submitted by Scenic Hudson and others; testimony before the Federal Power Commission; exhibits; legislation introduced in the New York State Assembly, U.S. Senate, and the House of Representatives; and related materials.
  - Rules of Practice and Procedure (Folder 798, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Brief (Folder 799, Box 67)
  - Petition of the SHPC for Permission to Intervene; 2/6/64 (Folder 800, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Initial Brief to FPC Examiner; 6/15/64 (Folder 801, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Reply Brief to Examiner: 6/30/64 (Folder 802, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Statement in Opposition to License Application of Consolidated Edison; 7/13/64 (Folder 803, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Brief on Exceptions; 8/28/64 (Folder 804, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Motion for Oral Argument; 9/9/64 (Folder 805, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Brief Opposing Exceptions of the SHPC 10/8/64 (Folder 806, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Motion for Hearing and Postponement of Oral Argument; 10/8/64 (Folder 807, Box 67)
  - Statement in Opposition to Con. Ed.; Presented by NYS Joint Legis. Comm. On Natural Resources, Nov. 19-20, 1964 (Folder 808, Box 67)
  - Commissioner Ross - Dissent - March 9, 1965; Storm King (Folder 809, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Motion for Stay of Opinion and Order Issuing License; 4/8/65 (Folder 810, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Application for Rehearing of Opinion&Order Issuing License&Petition to Reopen Proceedings; 4/8/65 (Folder 811, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Motion to: Transfer Hearing to N.Y., Provide an Adjourned Hearing, To Expand the Scope of the Hearings; 4/26/65 (Folder 812, Box 67)
  - Scenic Hudson Inc.: Application for Rehearing of Order Denying Motions and Petition to Reopen Proceedings, June 4, 1965 (Folder 813, Box 67)
  - Rebuttal Brief to 2nd Circuit; 6/11/65 (Folder 814, Box 67)
  - Motion to Dismiss and Brief for Respondent FPC, Sept. 9, 1965 (Folder 815, Box 67)
  - Petition - U.S. Court of Appeals, Oct. 1965 (Folder 816, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Answer of SHPC to Motion for the Production of Membership Lists&for Extension to Answer Petitions; 3/5/66 (Folder 817, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Motion for Vacation Dates, Holding of a Later Pre-Hearing Conference, and Stay of Proceedings; 4/14/66 (Folder 818, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Supplementary Inquiries Addressed to the Commission; 7/22/66 (Folder 819, Box 67)
  - SHPC - Motion for Clarification of Order Fixing Filing Schedule; 8/13/66 (Folder 820, Box 67)
  - Congressional Record; 9/6/66 (Folder 821, Box 68)
  - Catskill Aqueduct; Application Brief, Filed 9/19/66 (Folder 822, Box 68)
  - Summons: Harry Lewis vs. Con. Edison, et al; October 21, 1966 (Folder 823, Box 68)
  - Motion by S.H. to Defer Proceedings Re: Public Law 89-605 (Compact); 11/12/66 (Folder 824, Box 68)
  - S.H.’s Motion to Postpone Hearings; 12/14/66 (Folder 825, Box 68)
  - Reports on Legislation, 1966 (Folder 826, Box 68)
  - Brief on Behalf of Scenic Hudson, Inc. - Intervenor; 8/14/67 (Folder 827, Box 68)
  - Scenic Hudson Brief; Aug. 14, 1967 (Folder 828, Box 68)
  - Reply Brief, Town of Cornwall; Sept. 2, 1967 (Folder 829, Box 68)
  - Reply Brief, Town of Philipstown and Philipstown Citizens Association; 9/5/67 (Folder 830, Box 68)
  - FPC: 2338 9/5/67; SHPC Reply Brief (Folder 831, Box 68)
  - Views and Comments of SHPC, Dec. ’67 - Re: Annual Report (Folder 832, Box 68)
  - Request by S.H. to FPC for Additional Information to be Supplied by Con. Ed.; 2/14/68 (Folder 833, Box 69)
  - Petition for Extension of Time by S. Hudson; 8/1/68 (Folder 834, Box 69)
  - Presiding Examiner’s Initial Decision; Aug. 6, 1968 (Folder 835, Box 69)
  - Brief on Exceptions to Examiner’s Report of 8/6/68 for Other Groups (Draft) (Folder 836, Box 69)
  - Mini Brief on Exceptions; 10/7/68 (Folder 837, Box 69)
  - Excerpts from Brief on Exceptions; 10/10/68 (Folder 838, Box 69)
  - S.H. Attorney Letter to FPC and S.H. Reply Brief Opposing Exceptions, and Revised pp. I-25; 10/28/68 (Folder 839, Box 69)
  - Brief on Exceptions to Initial Decision; 10/28/68 (Folder 840, Box 69)
  - Motions by S.H. - Re: New Hearings; 12/19/68 (Folder 841, Box 69)
  - Working Committee on Utilities - Report to the Vice President and President’s Council on Recreation and Natural Beauty; 12/27/68 (Folder 842, Box 69)
  - Reply Brief - Scenic Hudson before Simpson: Exam. for FPC; Dec. 68 or 69 (Folder 843, Box 69)
  - Award to SHPC - Conservation Organization of the Year; 2/17/69 (Folder 844, Box 69)
  - FDC - 1969: Stipulation Limiting Scope of Cost Evidence; 2/27/69 (Folder 845, Box 69)
  - SHPC - Brief; 4/25/69 (Folder 846, Box 69)
  - Scenic Hudson Reply Brief to FPC; 5/23/69 (Folder 847, Box 69)
  - S.H. Attorney’s Letter to FPC; 7/8/69 (Folder 848, Box 69)
  - Minutes to Public Hearing, NYS Public Service Comm.; 9/26/69 (Folder 849, Box 70)
  - Minutes of Hearing, NYS Public Service Comm.; 10/21/69 (Folder 850, Box 70)
  - United States of America Federal Power Commission, Consolidated Edison; Dec. 23, 1969 (Folder 851, Box 70)
  - S.H. Brief on Exception to Examiners; 12/23/69 (Folder 852, Box 70)
  - FPC: 2338, 2/10/70; SHPC Exceptions to 12/23/69 Decision (Folder 853, Box 70)
  - Scenic Hudson Letters to Intervenors; Jan. 1970 (Folder 854, Box 70)
  - Brief Opposing Exceptions - Scenic Hudson; 3/30/70 (Folder 855, Box 70)
  - S.H. Motion for Oral Argument; 3/3/70 (Folder 856, Box 70)
  - Final Argument in FPC Case, Storm King - Draft; 3/19/70 (Folder 857, Box 70)
  - Opinion and Order Issuing License; Aug. 19, 1970 (Folder 858, Box 70)
  - ACT - Hudson River Compact; 1966&1970 (Folder 859, Box 70)
  - Brief on Behalf of Scenic Hudson; Mar. 1, 1971 (Folder 860, Box 70)
  - Court of Appeals Reply Brief - SHPC; 5/4/71 (Folder 861, Box 70)
  - Scenic Hudson, et al vs. FPC and Con. Ed. - Petitions for Review, U.S. Court of Appeals, June 9. 1971 (Folder 862, Box 71)
  - N.Y.S. Water Quality Issue; 7/2/71 (Folder 863, Box 71)
  - S.H. Brief on Water Quality Ctfn. (Sec. 21-B); Aug. 10, 1971 (Folder 864, Box 71)
  - Report of Hearing Officer, NYS Department of Environmental Conservation; 8/12/71 (Folder 865, Box 71)
  - Briefs, S - 36; 12/10/71 (Folder 866, Box 71)
  - Water Quality (NYS Supreme Court); Dec. 15, 1971 (Folder 867, Box 71)
  - Berle and Butzel (Legal); 1971-72 (Folder 868, Box 71)
  - Petitions, NYS Supreme Court; Feb 11, 1972 (Folder 869, Box 71)
  - S.H. Reply Brief, Supreme Court NYS - Henry Diamond; 2/25/72 (Folder 870, Box 71)
  - John Clark, NYS Affidavit; Feb. 1972 (Folder 871, Box 71)
  - Federal Supreme Court Petition for Certiorari; 3/24/72 (Folder 872, Box 71)
  - Order and Judgement (PITT), NYS Supreme Court; March 31, 1972 (Folder 873, Box 71)
  - Brief for Petitioners - Respondents; May 19, 1972 (Folder 874, Box 71)
  - Douglas Dissent, Supreme Court; 6/19/72 (Folder 875, Box 71)
  - Appellate Court Reversal; 6/29/72 (Folder 876, Box 71)
  - SHPC/ETC, vs. EC/CE Cornwall, Re: Art. 78 CPLR - Brief for SHPC; 11/27/72 (Folder 877, Box 71)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, 1972, Petition for Certiorari (Folder 878, Box 71)